(Howard:)And this is a woman who kept
a safety rail on my bed until I was 17.
(Mrs Koothrappali:)So she has no problem
with her son being eaten by a walrus?
(Sheldon:)That's very unlikely, Mrs. Koothrappali.
(Sheldon:)If Raj dies, it'll be from frostbite,
gangrene, acute sunburn...
(Sheldon:)...or being ripped to shreds
by a 1500-pound polar bear.
(Howard:)Ma, I'm putting you on speakerphone
with Raj's parents.
(Howard:)Can you tell them that you're okay
with me going to the Arctic?
MRS. WOLOWITZ [ON SPEAKERPHONE]:
Arctic? I thought you said Arkansas.
(Howard:)I didn't say that.
You never listen to me.
(Howard's Mother:)He doesn't tell me anything.
(Howard's Mother:)He lives a secret life
because he's ashamed.
(Penny:)Hey, Leonard,
can I talk to you for a sec?
(Leonard:)Sure, but let's go out here where
there's a little less yelling and guilt.
(Leonard:)What's up?
(Penny:)Well, I got you
a little going-away present.
- Oh, a blanket.
- Oh, no, no. Not just a blanket.
(Penny:)See, it has sleeves.